4insureusa.com 2008-08-14

# 4insureusa.com - Privacy Policy

4insureusa.com Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Public Citizen does not automatically collect personal information. If you choose to give us your name, address, phone number, or issues of interest, we may store this information to keep you posted on relevant activities. Please read below to learn how your privacy is protected. 

Except as noted below, we do not enable cookies or use other software or hardware techniques to collect personal information on visitors to our site without their knowledge. We log IP addresses, or the location of your computer or network on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We also use IP addresses in the aggregate to track which pages people visit in order to improve the quality of the site. We do not use these data to develop profiles of individual visitors to our Web site. There is no personal information collected in our automated log files. We evaluate site usage by analyzing user information in the aggregate, but this analysis does not identify any individual user. 

When you contact us for information: We maintain some records of individuals who contact us for information in case we need contact them later or provide further information. However, we do not provide this information to anyone else unless you give us your permission or unless disclosure is compelled by law. Individual information about website visitors, including e-mail addresses, is never shared with third parties. 

We may disclose the information described above to: 

Insurance agents or insurance companies as needed to fulfill your rate requests; 

Companies that perform technology or marketing services for us, and are prohibited to share that information with others; 

To others only if you consent or as permitted by law. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, please email us.
